pluscrack.com 2014-07-04

# Privacy Policy

Details
     Last Updated on Saturday, 01 February 2014 12:40 

**Introduction**  
We respect your privacy and want to make your experience using our Services as enjoyable and rewarding as possible. We collect information in different ways from Users who may access our Services, or the network of websites accessible through our Services. We use this information primarily to provide a customized experience as you use our Services and, generally, do not share this information with third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected if we have received your permission beforehand, when we believe that such disclosure is required by law, or in certain other cases as described below.

**Partners and Sponsors**  
Some Services are offered or promoted to Users in conjunction with a partner or sponsor. We may share certain personal information (such as a Subscriber's name and email) but no billing information with our partner or sponsor in order to provide the relevant Services or run the promotion. Additionally, we may have some co-branded campaigns that are co-sponsored by non-affiliated partners. We may share non-identifying and aggregate information as part of these campaigns in order to administer the co-branded products or services offered, but do not share personally identifiable information of individual Subscribers with such non-affiliated partners.

**Online Advertisements**  
We do not share personally identifiable information about individual Users with advertisers. We may display online advertisements and we may share aggregated and non-identifying information about our Users that we collect through the registration process or through online surveys and promotions with certain advertisers. In some instances, we use this aggregated and non-identifying information to deliver tailored advertisements. For example, an advertiser may tell us the audience they want to reach (e.g., males between 25 and 55 years of age) and provide us with an advertisement tailored to the audience. Based upon the aggregated and non-identifying information we have collected, we may then display the advertisement to the intended audience.

**"Cookies" and How We Use Them**  
A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain websites or open certain emails. We may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the products and Services we provide and to manage our telecommunications networks. More specifically, we use (i) "required cookies" which are required for our website to work, (ii) "performance cookies" which allow us to analyze how Visitors use our website so we can measure and improve the performance of our website, (iii) "functional cookies" which allow us to remember choices you may have made on our website, and (iv) "advertising cookies" which are used to present ads that are relevant to your interests. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your personal information. You may set your Web browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. However, if you decide not to accept cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of all of the features of our website. Additionally, be aware that if you visit third party websites where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable, you may be required to accept cookies. Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them. We may utilize cookies to track referrals from internal and external affiliates, as well as advertising campaigns. We may also use a third party service provider to send emails that you have agreed to receive. Pixel tags and cookies may be used in those email messages to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising, how our Visitors use our website and to enable us to provide more focused marketing communications to you.

**Widgets**  
Our website includes social media features (such as the Facebook "Like" button). These features may collect your IP address and which page you are visiting on our website, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets may be hosted by a third party or directly on our website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the feature.

**Statistics**  
We use information gathered from our website statistics (for example, User IP addresses) to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer our website. We also gather broad demographic information from this data to help us improve our website and make your browsing and purchasing experience more enjoyable. Any statistics gathered by us are proprietary property of the Company.

**Terms of Use**  
This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to our Terms of Service.

**Revisions to This Policy**  
We reserve the right to revise, amend, or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and in any manner. However, if we plan to materially change how we plan to use previously collect personal information, we will provide you with advance notice prior to the change becoming effective and an opportunity to opt-out of such differing uses. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
